≡ƒöì Inspecting order: FRK-XE-20260421-1030AM
Platform: Forkable
Date: 2026-04-21
Items:
- 1x Bangkok Pepper Tofu Noodles (Add Side: Spring Roll with Thai Sweet Chilli)
- 6x Spring Roll with Thai Sweet Chilli 
- 1x Charcoal-Grilled BBQ Chicken Noodles (Add Side: Spring Roll with Thai Sweet Chilli)
- 1x Charcoal-Grilled BBQ Chicken Noodles (Add Side: Gyoza with Green Chilli Mayo)
- 3x Gyoza with Green Chilli Mayo 
- 2x Charcoal-Grilled BBQ Chicken Rice 
- 1x Green Curry Charcoal-Grilled BBQ Chicken Rice (Add Side: Spring Roll with Thai Sweet Chilli)
- 1x Green Curry Hatyai Crispy Chicken Rice (Add Side: Gyoza with Green Chilli Mayo)
- 1x Green Curry Hatyai Crispy Chicken Rice (Add Side: Spring Roll with Thai Sweet Chilli)
- 1x Green Curry Hatyai Crispy Chicken Rice 
- 2x Hatyai Crispy Chicken Rice (Add Side: Spring Roll with Thai Sweet Chilli)
- 3x Hatyai Crispy Chicken Rice 
- 3x OG Pad Thai With Charcoal-Grilled BBQ Chicken 
- 2x OG Pad Thai With Hatyai Crispy Chicken 
- 1x OG Pad Thai With Hatyai Crispy Chicken (Add Side: Gyoza with Green Chilli Mayo)
- 1x ROSA P 
